we learned that Sweden now has their own
phone number to finally get those
confusing Ikea instructions translated
and I ask you to tell me what you might
hear if you called the America number
let's dial it in katop let's start with
you all right you've reached America
before we get started I'd like to First
apologize for the senseless Wars the
Kardashians the Republican Party the
Democratic party and of course Carrot
Top very sorry I'm so
sorry very sorry
thank you what are you laughing about
Aron thank you for calling America we
can't come to the phone right now
because we're morbidly obese and the
phone is way over
there if you want to start a war press
one or to talk to Emperor Trump stay on
the
line all
right Leon I like
it hey hey what's going on you reach
America is Adam and Eve not Adam and
Steve you sum a because if God
wanted it that way he wanted two dudes
to be doing all this kind of stuff he
would have made them that way but
instead he got a whole here and got
thing there for babies to come out of
all
[Applause]
right leave your m is this thing still
recording what
the